<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Hardware - Category - H4ndSH</title>
        <link>https://h4ndsh.github.io/categories/hardware/</link>
        <description>Hardware - Category - H4ndSH</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>h4ndsh@outlook.com (h4ndsh)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>h4ndsh@outlook.com (h4ndsh)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://h4ndsh.github.io/categories/hardware/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Building a local AI server with multiple GPUs using MCP and Ollama</title>
    <link>https://h4ndsh.github.io/2025/ai-server/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>h4ndsh</author>
    <guid>https://h4ndsh.github.io/2025/ai-server/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hardware Components Here is a summary of the components used in this build. Each component was chosen to provide a balance of performance, stability, and scalability for AI workloads.
Component Model Quantity Motherboard ASUS Pro WS WRX80E-SAGE SE 1 CPU AMD Ryzen Threadripper PRO 5975WX 1 RAM 128GB Samsung DDR4-3200 ECC 4x32GB NVMe SSD Samsung 990 Pro 1TB 1 Enterprise SSD Kingston DC600M 1.92TB 1 Case Silverstone SST-RM51 1 PSU FSP CANNON PRO 2500W 1 GPU NVIDIA RTX 5090 32GB 2 CPU Cooler Noctua NH-U9 TR4-SP3 1 A picture of the server components Montagem do PC software]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Exploring the Versatile Flipper Zero: First Impressions and Hands-On</title>
    <link>https://h4ndsh.github.io/2023/flipperzero/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>h4ndsh</author>
    <guid>https://h4ndsh.github.io/2023/flipperzero/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I recently acquired a Flipper Zero, a multi-tool device that can be used for a variety of tasks, including security research, hardware hacking, and DIY electronics. In this blog post, I will share my first impressions of the Flipper Zero, as well as some of the projects I have been working on with it.
I am excited to explore all of the possibilities that the Flipper Zero has to offer. I believe that it is a valuable tool for anyone who is interested in security, hardware, or electronics.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
